# Ivanchuk Ivan, Kotlin-backend developer

(+7) 988-061-84-72 | l3r8y@duck.com | t.me.l3r8y | blog | github.com/l3r8yJ | linkedin

## About

I have my own open source projects, one of them is a <u>Ruby library</u>. It has reached **9k+ downloads**. You can find it and other projects or contributions to OSS in my <u>GitHub account</u>. I have experience in <u>teaching students</u> in the discipline *Theory of Formal Languages*. Also, member of jury KaiCode OSS festival.

# Experience

Samokat.tech | Kotlin Backend Developer | 23.10.2023 - present.

• Working on the clients tickets system. Developed a few OSS products during the working in project – checkout my GitHub account. Opened an <u>issue</u> at Spring Framework. Tried to <u>contribute</u> to DGS, but it was ignored.

Kotlin, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Gradle, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase, Jooq

VTB | Java Team Lead | 30.08.2023 - 23.10.2023.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment. Managing a team of 8 people. Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

VTB | Java Developer | 03.04.2023 - 30.08.2023.

- Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment.
- Added unit-tests linter to project. Found a bunch test anti-patterns in project, excluded part of them by contribution into linter.

Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

INTERVOLGA | 19.04.2022 - 04.08.2022

• B2B development. Worked on integration of 1c-bitrix PHP, 1c-bitrix framework, SQL

#### Skills

- Java, Kotlin | Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Gradle, Liquibase
- RDBMS | PostgreSQL
- CI/CD | GitHub Actions contributed to some GHAs
- Other | Ruby, Rust

# Education

### Volgograd State Technical University

Bachelor, Engineering and Economics, Software engineering